<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Expressions Artist Show]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Expressions Artist Show]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/augustshow/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 14:58:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/augustshow/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pueblo Pot
Cherry, Walnut, Wormy Red Maple]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong><a href="http://www.stevegermaine.com/" title="">Steve Germaine</a> -Fort Collins, Colorado, 2017</strong></p>,<p>“I make art because I have a desire to create something that when viewed elicits an emotional response”</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/babf39c6-a174-4639-8870-de3332578b1a.png">,<p>“A hope of contributing a little something beautiful now and then, and to be a supply-side participant in the trans formative power of art.”</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/97115554-8728-4a0c-aca4-2c67d98b0aaa.jpg" title="Pueblo Pot
Cherry, Walnut, Wormy Red Maple">,<p>Steve’s art is made using wood because wood and forests have been integral part of his . He grew up in the hardwood forests of New England, and began making wooden things at a young age, spent his career studying forest ecology, and returned to the forests for nourishment, inspiration, and recreation.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/augustshow/pueblo-pot-cherry-walnut-wormy-red-maple/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4fe6c126-12fa-48c0-a19a-0d6fe6acf1e2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 01:16:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spiritual Surrender by Patty Hughes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Patty Hughes</p>,<p>"I am a self taught artist who has been drawing and painting for about 20 years. I have attended many workshops by outstanding instructors, and I have won awards for my work over the years. I work mostly in watercolor, acrylic, collage and mixed media and enjoy creating abstract and non-objective pieces. Since I started painting late in life, I was not sure of my purpose, but felt the strong pull to discover what I was meant to create.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/164af83f-fefb-466f-a4d8-776981e53632.jpg">,<p>What a journey it has been and continues to be!! Much of my work is intuitive, discovering where I am going in a painting as I travel through the process. Some of my work is deliberate, perhaps a mixed media piece of an incredible mountain scene or an abstract representation of a raptor in flight. My love of nature and my surroundings is evident in my plein air pieces along with my work done in the studio. I hope that my work evokes emotion when the resulting product is revealed. I love to share the gift I have been given with others!"</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/023336c4-7470-42cd-badd-19ba7d35d944.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/augustshow/spiritual-surrender-by-patty-hughes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9df229a9-3ca9-484b-8855-934e2a00758e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 19:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>